

JAKUB KOSMAL

JUNIOR NETWORK ENGINEER

CONTACT

510-447-849

kubakosmal2@gmail.com

jakubkosmal.pl

Praga Południe 04-294 Warszawa, Poland

EDUCATION

Technik Mechatronik

Technikum nr 1 w Siedlcach

2017-2021

Specialization: Mechatronics
Technician Education level: secondary.

SKILLS

Junior level knowledge of **Frontend** and **Backend** Development:

- JavaScript
- Html
- CSS
- Vue Framework
- Docker
- Python

Driver's licence

Configuration and management of networks

Customer Comunication

PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT

I am currently in the process of preparing for the **Cisco CCNA** Exam. I am developing my skills in Web

Development, focusing on Vue libraries, and developing my knowledge of other technologies.

LANGUAGES

English



Communicative

ABOUT ME

My name is Jakub, I am 22 years old. My professional goal is to constantly develop myself by acquiring new skills, learning and taking on challenges. I am not afraid to face difficulties and can commit myself to work. I like to perform assigned tasks with honesty and integrity, which allows me to learn and organize my work effectively. I like to maintain good contact with customers and build positive relationships. It is important to me to leave a legacy of high quality work. I am a positive and open-minded person who has high ambitions and wants to grow through work and learning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Service Desk Operator

Intelligent Technologies S.A.

2022-Today

- Overseeing, maintaining and collecting information on failure reports of teletechnical systems, creating service requests.
- Repairing at 1st line support level, and supporting 2nd line operations through service and installation trips.
- Installing services, configuring equipment and maintaining repair records.
- Configuring LAN and WAN networks, managing firewalls, creating rules
- QoS and configuration of VPN tunnels using MikroTik devices.
- Configuration of Backbone Network on Cisco devices, using VLAN technologies.
- Technologies related to the creation of wireless computer networks using Ubiquiti devices.
- Designing, configuring and managing Wi-Fi networks, including configuring access points, creating guest networks, managing bandwidth, and monitoring and troubleshooting network performance.

Installer of alarm systems, CCTV, Access control systems

 $\label{eq:art-system} \textit{ART-SYSTEM} \textit{/} \textit{Megavision Technology Sp. z o.o.}$

2021-2022

- Configuration and installation of SATEL alarm systems, Avigilon CCTV monitoring and ROGER access control.
- Basic operation of AutoCad program (Making as-built documentation).
- Self-organization of work.
- Basic configuration of LAN, alarm systems, KD and CCTV systems.
- Installation of LAN wiring for CCTV services of alarm systems and access control.
- · Conducting inspections of alarm systems, CCTV, access control.

Driver at a car rental company

Yourcar24.pl 2020-2021

Bus International driver

PK Logistic / Central Europe 2020

Foreman, Paving Worker

Mar-Bud 2018-2021